http://www.drugsense.org/cms/privacy

Skip to Content
Home
DrugSense/Media Awareness Project Inc. Privacy Policy
Effective
as of July 27, 2010.
1	INTRODUCTION
We take the privacy of members of,
and visitors to, the http://www.mapinc.org/, http://www.drugpolicycentral.com/ and
http://www.drugsense.org/ websites (the “Service”) very seriously. Please read this
Privacy Policy to learn more about how the Media Awareness Project Inc. (“MAP,” “we,” our,” or “us”) treats information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with the Service. We provide this Privacy Policy because visitors to our websites have a right to know what information we
collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at
or by post at:
DrugSense,
14252 Culver Drive #328,
Irvine, CA
92604-0326.
Online
Privacy Standards. We
follow the principles supported by the Federal Trade Commission’s
Fair Information Practices Principles, currently available at
http://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy3/fairinfo.shtm.
What
This Policy Covers.
This policy covers the ways in which MAP treats information,
including personally identifiable information, which we obtain when
you use our Service. We regard personally identifiable information as
information that someone can use to identify or contact you in
person, such as your real name, telephone number, birth date, email
address,
or physical mailing address. Neither the technical information
associated with your access to the Service – such as your
internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider
(ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and
click stream data – nor information that we use internally to
identify you as a user in our system is considered personally
identifiable information.
What
This Policy Does Not Cover.
This policy does not cover the privacy practices of third parties
that we do not own or control. In addition, we may provide links to
other services and on occasion to other sites that may interest you.
All of these sites operate independently of MAP and each has its own
privacy and security practices. For your best on-line experience, we
encourage you to review each website’s privacy and security
policies before submitting any personal information to that website.
you choose to subscribe to our email newsletter, you will be asked to
provide a valid email address.
When You Upload Content.
When you chose to
upload content to the Service, you will be asked to provide a valid
email address.
When
You Email Content. The
Service makes it possible for you email content located on the server
to third parties and to yourself. When you choose to email content
using this feature, you will be asked to provide a valid email
address.
When
You Donate. When you
choose to donate to MAP, you will be asked to provide information
sufficient to complete your donation (e.g., your credit card
information, billing address, etc.), along with a valid email
address.
Information
We Do Not Collect From Any Users
Children
.
As explained further in our Terms of Use (available at
http://www.drugsense.org/terms_of_use),
you must be 18 years of age or older – or, if you are under the
age of majority in your jurisdiction, have the consent of your parent
or guardian – to use the Service. Therefore, we do not
knowingly collect personally identifiable information from or about
children. In accordance with Federal Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), MAP will never
knowingly solicit, nor will we accept, personally identifiable
information from visitors known to be under thirteen (13) years of
age. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone
under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at
, or write to our
Privacy Officer at the address noted above.
Information
We Track
Log Files.
Similar to many websites and internet services, we gather certain
anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web
server log files. This information includes internet protocol
addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), site
entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream
data. We use this information to improve our site, analyze trends,
administer the site, and gather aggregate information about our user
base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a
group or category of services or users from which individual user
identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your
personally identifiable information.
Cookies.
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for
record-keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site
visitors arrive at our site and what pages they view during their
visit. Similar to many websites, the Service stores an encrypted
cookie on your computer so we can remember you when you come back
without requiring you to log in each time. Cookies also allow us to
track and understand the interests of our visitors and to enhance the
overall experience on our Service. Cookies used by MAP do not include
your personally identifiable information
If
you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your web browser
software to disable them. To do so, please refer to the help section
of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or
disable cookies. Please note that your browser must be configured to
accept cookies to use some components of the Service.
use emails and/or prominent notifications on our website as our
primary means to inform our users of important Service announcements.
Email
Subscription Services.
We use the email address you provide us to deliver information from
MAP – and other like-minded entities – to you. These
communications are purely optional, and each such communication will
contain a prominent “unsubscribe” link to allow you to
opt out of such communications going forward. There are also forms
online where you can opt out of receiving future emails located at
http://www.drugsense.org/lists/
and
http://www.mapinc.org/lists/.
On
Our Website
When
Sharing Content. When
you chose to share content using the Service, you will be asked to
provide your first and last name and email address. This information
will appear online in connection with the content you have shared.
Please do not include any personally identifiable information which
you choose not to share in any field that will accompany the content.
Site
Statistics. As noted
above, we use information collected from our web log files to
calculate and publish anonymous, non-personal, aggregate statistics
that we believe our users are interested in viewing. For example, we
may track and publish the total number of users who have viewed a
particular piece of published content. We publish this data in
aggregate form only, and do not tie it to any personally identifiable
information.
When
You Donate. When you
donate to MAP, we store the information you provide to contact you
later regarding MAP and the Service.
For
Internal Reporting and Analysis
As
noted above, we use information gathered from log files and cookies
to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, track the
movement of users around the site, and to gather aggregate
information about our user base as a whole. We do not tie this data
to personally identifiable information.
4	HOW
WE SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION
With
Third-Parties
Sharing,
Renting, and Selling Information We Collect.
We will neither rent nor sell your personally identifiable
information to anyone. We may share your personally identifiable
information, including your email address, with like-minded entities
for the purpose of furthering the mission of MAP to inform the
public. Occasionally we also share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate
information about our user base with third parties, and we may
publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the
interest of our users. We do not tie this aggregate usage data to the
personally identifiable information of any person.
Linked
Services. In some
cases, we allow you to access or link to other web services through
our website. We make it easy for you to determine when you are
accessing or linking to these other web services through our website.
In all of these cases, those sites may choose to collect your
personal information as they deem appropriate. As noted above, we are
not responsible for or in control of how third parties collect, use,
or disclose your information obtained through these linked services.
We encourage you to be aware when you are using these third party
services and, for your best on-line experience, we encourage you to
review their policies before submitting any personal information to
them.
As
Necessary In Certain Legal Circumstances
Legal
Requirements. We
reserve the right to disclose your information, including personally
identifiable information, when we have a good faith belief that
access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such information is
necessary to (a) comply with any law, regulation, legal process or
enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce these Terms of Use,
including investigation of potential violations of these Terms of
Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or
technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property
or safety of MAP, its users, or the public as required or permitted
by law.
Acquisition.
If MAP becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale
of some or all of its assets, including bankruptcy, our assets,
including user information, may be transferred to a third party. At
that time, your user information may become subject to that third
party’s privacy policy. Before we transfer your user
information, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our
site.
5	HOW
WE KEEP INFORMATION SECURE
Security
of Account Information.
MAP employs standard commercial security measures to maintain and
protect the safety and confidentiality of your personal information.
6	UPDATES
TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
From
time to time we will review, and may make changes to, our privacy
policy. When we do so, we will either notify you by email or by
placing a prominent notice on the Service. The most recent version of
